#### Felisha Garces

12227 Quail Dr. Apt.110

Balch Springs, Texas

Phone: 214-909-6807

Email: Felisha butterfly@yahoo.com

# **Objective**

To obtain a position with an established company that provides excellent client care and to use my skills and work ethic to provide care.

## **Professional Summary**

Highly experienced facilitation service provider, with proven skills and expertise in home health and long term care. Strong communicator with ability to interface with multiple levels of management through verbal and written skills set. Excellent track record in quick books, quarterly reports, problems solving, multitasking, scheduling, and patient care.

## **Technology Skills**

Windows 95/98/00/XP, Microsoft Office Word/Power Point, Typing Speed 45 wpm, excel, HMS, Eclipsys

#### History

Martinez Cleaning Service

501 Sunnyhill Dr. Tyler, Texas 75702 (903)780-2367

#### 12/2006-01/2012

Facilitation Service Provider

Schedule times for my company to come out and clean the facility.

Worked with financial depositions.

Assigned different employees to their designated site.

Assisted with housekeeping duties in apartments businesses and homes.

Received phone calls from clients that needed our services.

Went over contracts with clients that wanted our service.

Went over pricing with clients regarding our service.

Kept track of all inventory before and after shifts.

Made the schedules for the employees.

## · Balch Springs Nursing And Rehabilitation

4200 Shepherd Ln. Balch Springs, Texas 75180

(972)286-0335

5/16/2012-5/2015

CNA/ Scheduling Assistant

Worked closely with ADON and DON to provide the best schedule possible

Assisted with transporting patients safely to activities and Dr. Appt.

Provided excellent patient care

Assisted with filing all documents

Provided awesome all around customer care

## Baylor Institute for Rehabilitation

909 N. Washington Ave., Dallas, Texas 75246

4/25/2014-Current

Rehab assistant/ PRN unit secretary (01/2015)

Provide patient care and help patient return to their normal routine

Allow patient to perform ADLs with as minimal assistance to maximize independence.

Also file Doctor's orders, complete orders in HMS and/or Eclipsys

Admit/ discharge patients

Provide all around great customer service

### Education

- · John Tyler High School Diploma 5/2007 Diploma
- **Progressive Learning Center** 4/23/2012 Certified Nursing Assistant